{
    "Course 1": [
        {
            "question": "Question 1*",
            "optionA": "Hello 1",
            "optionB": "Bye 1",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionA",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 2*",
            "optionA": "Hello 2",
            "optionB": "Bye 2",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionA",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 3*",
            "optionA": "Hello 3",
            "optionB": "Bye 3",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionA",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 4*",
            "optionA": "Hello 4",
            "optionB": "Bye 4",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionA",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 5*",
            "optionA": "Hello 5",
            "optionB": "Bye 5",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionA",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 6*",
            "optionA": "Hello 6",
            "optionB": "Bye 6",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionA",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 7*",
            "optionA": "Hello 7",
            "optionB": "Bye 7",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionC",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 8*",
            "optionA": "Hello 8",
            "optionB": "Bye 8",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionB",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 9*",
            "optionA": "Hello 9",
            "optionB": "Bye 9",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionC",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
        {
            "question": "Question 10*",
            "optionA": "Hello 10",
            "optionB": "Bye 10",
            "optionC": "Both A&B",
            "optionD": "null",
            "answer": "optionB",
            "feedback": "Here is feedback"
        },
    ]
}
